shiftconmedia.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy - Shiftconmedia

shiftconmedia.com is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to shiftconmedia.com and to keeping personal information that visitors provide us private. We have established procedures and policies to ensure that the privacy of each visitor to shiftconmedia.com is protected. The following is a description of the information that we collect, how we will use the information and how we protect visitor information we collect. We request that you read the following description of our Privacy Policies and if you have any questions or comments, please contact us at info@shiftconmedia.com.

**Information That We Collect and How We Will Use It**

We will collect and maintain certain basic personally identifying information (“Personal Information”) about you when you contact us by e-mail and give us your personal information. Personal Information we collect will include such items as your name and e-mail address. We will use this information to respond to your requests for information. In addition, we may use Personal Information to send you information and news about additions to shiftconmedia.com and we may from time to time request additional Personal Information that we will use to better tailor our content to your needs. When we collect Personal Information from you, we will ask whether or not you want to be contacted by us.

In addition to Personal Information, our Web servers will collect and store general information about you that cannot be used to personally identify you. Such information includes the name of the domain and the host from which you access the Internet, the IP (Internet Protocol) address of your computer, your Internet browser and operating system, the time you accessed shiftconmedia.com and the Web site from which you linked to shiftconmedia.com, if any. We will use this information to monitor the use of shiftconmedia.com. We will also use this non-personal information to improve and modify shiftconmedia.com and we may share this non-personal information with third parties in aggregate form.

**Dissemination of Information to Third Parties**

shiftconmedia.com will not sell, rent, loan or share your Personal Information with any third parties, unless you have authorized us to do so or we are legally required to do so. shiftconmedia.com may provide non-personal information, which will not allow you to be identified or contacted, in aggregate form to third parties.

**Security**

shiftconmedia.com uses commercially reasonable computer security technology selected and implemented to ensure adherence to the privacy policies described in this online posting. All information contained or collected on shiftconmedia.com is protected using encryption programs.

**Cookies**

A “Cookie” is a small text file that we place on your computer’s hard drive that allows us to keep track of your activities on shiftconmedia.com. We will use Cookies to let us know whether you have visited shiftconmedia.com before and to help us generate content that may be of interest to you.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our site may provide links to other Web sites. The privacy policies described here for shiftconmedia.com do NOT apply to those external links. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other sites you visit. Be informed. You are the person best qualified to protect your own privacy.

**Your Consent**

By accessing shiftconmedia.com, you consent to the use of this information by shiftconmedia.com. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy in the future we will post the changes on this page. If any such change relates to a change in how we use your Personal Information, we will provide you with the option to consent to the change, or have your Personal Information removed from shiftconmedia.com.

**Changes to this Policy**

This Privacy Policy will always be available to users on this page for you to read. We will update this Privacy Policy to reflect new features, services and options, as well as any other changes with regard to the use of personal information.
